Guide to the Dr. Huey P. Newton Foundation Inc. Collection
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2: Black Panther Party Records, 2
  - Subseries 6: Legal, 6
    - [Gibson case] [1 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Crim. 12598;Sup. Ct. No. 4150
    - [Gibson case] [2 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - [Gibson v. People] (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Black Panther Party vs. Granny Goose, et. al. [1 of 2]1972 - 1973 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Case no. 429556
    - Black Panther Party vs. Granny Goose, et. al. [2 of 2]1972 - 1973 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Terrence Kayo Hallinan vs. John Mitchell1969 - 1972 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Case no. C-75-0558-RHS
    - Terrence Kayo Hallinan vs. John Mitchell1969 - 1972 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Fred Hampton Trial Documents [1 of 5] (Box 36, Folder 10)
      Case no. 70-C-1384
    - Fred Hampton Trial Documents [2 of 5] (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Fred Hampton Trial Documents [3 of 5] (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Fred Hampton Trial Documents [4 of 5] (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Fred Hampton Trial Documents [5 of 5] (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - [Hampton, et al case] [1 of 2] (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - [Hampton, et al case] [2 of 2] (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - [Iberia Hampton, et al vs. The City of Chicago, et al] [1 of 2] (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - [Iberia Hampton, et al vs. The City of Chicago, et al] [2 of 2] (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - [People v. Hilliard, et.al. - Grand Jury Minutes] [1 of 4]1968 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - [People v. Hilliard, et.al. - Grand Jury Minutes] [2 of 4]1968 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - [People v. Hilliard, et.al. - Grand Jury Minutes] [3 of 4]1968 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - [People v. Hilliard, et.al. - Grand Jury Minutes] [4 of 4]1968 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Affidavit - Robert V. Hughes - C.S.R.1985 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Lawsuit - Original Complaint BPP v. Levi 12/761976 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - BPP vs. Levi Initial Brief (& Copies) Filed Dec. 1, 1976 1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Black Panther Party v. Levi 577-3CRG file opened 5/5/77 [1 of 3] (Box 38, Folder 5)
      76-2205
    - Black Panther Party v. Levi 577-3CRG file opened 5/5/77 [2 of 3] (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Black Panther Party v. Levi 577-3CRG file opened 5/5/77 [3 of 3] (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - BPP vs. Levi: initial (BPP's) response to govt's interrogatory in suit (Filed 8/26/77)1977 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - 8-26-77 Response (E.Brown) [BPP v. Levi]1977 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - BPP vs. Levi 12/1/76 1977 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - BPP vs. Levi Folder [1 of 3]1978 - 1980 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      80-1302; 76-2205
    - BPP vs. Levi Folder [2 of 3]1978 - 1980 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - BPP vs. Levi Folder [3 of 3]1978 - 1980 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - BPP vs. Levi: Correspondence & Memorandums [1 of 2]1975 - 1979 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - BPP vs. Levi: Correspondence & Memorandums [2 of 2]1975 - 1979 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - [BPP, et al. v. Edward Levi, et al.] [1 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - [BPP, et al. v. Edward Levi, et al.] [2 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - [BPP, et al. v. Edward Levi, et al.] [3 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - [BPP, et al. v. Edward Levi, et al.] [4 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - [BPP, et al. v. Edward Levi, et al.] [5 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - [BPP v. Edward Levi] (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Amended Version: BPP vs. Levi1977 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Case of Several LA. Party members - July 19711971 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - State of Ca vs. LA Panthers 9/3/711971 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Mosher, Tom #11768 "Scope Project on Political Surveillance" CRG [1 of 2]1968 - 1977 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      11415; 42287; 12848
    - Mosher, Tom #11768 "Scope Project on Political Surveillance" CRG [2 of 2]1968 - 1977 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      11415
    - Oakland Police Dept - Crime Report Kathleen Smith 8-741974 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Superior Court: Petition for A Writ of Habeas Corpus [Geronimo]79 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Case #69-107
    - Transportes, etc. v. Ronair, Inc., et al. file opened 10/11/84 1084-12CRG (Box 40, Folder 2)
      Case no. 81 Civ. 120 (JLL)
    - Santa Barbara School District vs. State of California1972 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Case #LA 30054
    - Chairman Bobby Seale and Ericka Huggins Trial (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - State of CA vs. Melvin C. Smith 1-20-711971 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      A253348
    - [Spain et al v. Procunier et al] [1 of 3] (Box 40, Folder 6)
      Case #C73-1293-AJZ
    - [Spain et al v. Procunier et al] [2 of 3] (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - [Spain et al v. Procunier et al] [3 of 3] (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Newton, Huey P. (Washington, Bruce) People vs. (Vio. 12031PC & 417PC) 7/30/74 #64620 8/9/74 CRG 1974 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - [People v. Wells & Bursey] (Box 40, Folder 10)
      Crim. No. 11415
    - [People v. Wells] (Box 40, Folder 11)
      Crim. No. 8712
    - Consumer Affairs - Bureau of Collection and Investigative Services [1 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      Superior Court no.225211
    - Consumer Affairs - Bureau of Collection and Investigative Services [2 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      3 Civ. 13961; Superior Court no. 225211
    - Re: Incumbents Appearing First on Ballot By Law1972 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      SAC 7951
    - [Amended class action complaint for declaratory and injunctive relief and damages] (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Petitions (Legal Documents)1970 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      Case no. 47574
    - Double Jeopardy1971 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      Civil Action no. 2761
  - Subseries 7: Individuals, 7
    - Elaine Brown
      - Elaine Brown - Corresp. 1975 - 1977 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Elaine Resigns From the B.P.P.1977 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Elaine Brown - A Thirst for Violence? - S.F. Chronicle May 3, 1993 1993 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Elaine Brown - Angela Davis Interview1972 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - [Elaine Brown's song lyrics] (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Elaine Brown Records1972 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Eldridge Cleaver
      - Eldridge Cleaver1975 - 1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
        C77-1423
      - Eldridge Cleaver Articles (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Right On Eldridge Cleaver's Paper (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - [Black Eldridge] 1970 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Eldridge Cleaver: By Jay Ceballos - March 17, 19711971 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Angela Davis
      - Angela Davis1970 - 1972 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Angela Davis by Genet (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Ruchell Magee and Angela Davis [1 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Ruchell Magee and Angela Davis [2 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Ruchell Magee and Angela Davis [3 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Angela Davis - Ericka Huggins Book [1 of 3]1970 - 1972 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Angela Davis - Ericka Huggins Book [2 of 3]1970 - 1972 (Box 42, Folder 1)
        some Stronghold items;part of the first draft of "Hidden Traitor Renegade Scab"
      - Angela Davis - Ericka Huggins Book [3 of 3]1970 - 1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Angela Davis Movie1970 - 1971 (Box 42, Folder 3)
        includes George Jackson article for the New York Times (11/16/70) from San Quentin
    - Donald Freed
      - Donald Freed [1 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 4)
        includes photos of Huey Newton with various people
      - Donald Freed [2 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 5)
        included are "Fidel on the Grassy Knoll: the Death of a Lie" by Donald Freed and Jeff Cohen and;"The Monster and the Spectacle: Reflections on Mary Hartman, Mary Hartman" by Kalina Charwat and Donald Freed
      - Letters From Don Freed [1 of 3]1972 - 1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Letters From Don Freed [2 of 3]1972 - 1974 (Box 42, Folder 7)
        "The Liberation Army that Sat by the Door" A Report of the Citizens Research and Investigation Committee
      - Letters From Don Freed [3 of 3]1972 - 1974 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Body-Counting the Panthers by Donald Freed1971 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Oakland and the World [by Donald Freed]1972 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Babylon: By Mark Lane and Donald Freed1970 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Don Freed Article1971 (Box 42, Folder 12)
        "Body Counting the Panthers"
    - Charles Garry
      - Charles Garry1977 - 1978 (Box 42, Folder 13)
        includes "The Public Eye" (vol 1, no. 2, April 1978)
      - Charles R. Garry1971 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Charles Garry - Misc Corresp. including CIA (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - [Charles R. Garry -Tape #12] (Box 43, Folder 1)
        transcripts
      - 115 Reference Cards Legal Notes/Misc (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - [Idaho Trial Lawyers Association - Seminar Material] [1 of 3]1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
        Idaho Supreme Court Case Review 1977 1978;Packagin Voir Dire, Opening and Closing Argument
      - [Idaho Trial Lawyers Association - Seminar Material] [2 of 3]1978 (Box 43, Folder 4)
        Idaho State Constitution;Expediting Voir Dire: An Empirical Study
      - [Idaho Trial Lawyers Association - Seminar Material] [3 of 3]1978 (Box 43, Folder 5)
        The Criminal Law Jury: Selection and Persuasion
    - Fred Hampton
      - Fred Hampton - Biog. - Don Johnson (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - [Hampton case]1969 - 1977 (Box 43, Folder 7)
        case # 70 - 1384 plus ballistic information
    - Robert Heard
      - [California v. Heard - Vol. I] [1 of 3] (Box 43, Folder 8)
        case # 66517
      - [California v. Heard - Vol. I] [2 of 3] (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - [California v. Heard - Vol. I] [3 of 3] (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - [California v. Heard - Vol. II] [1 of 2] (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - [California v. Heard - Vol. II] [2 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - [California v. Heard - Vol. III] [1 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - [California v. Heard - Vol. III] [2 of 2] (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Ericka Huggins
      - [Erika Huggins]1977 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Servant: Insights and Poems [1 of 2]1971 - 1975 (Box 44, Folder 5)
        publication plus contracts and poetry by Ericka
      - Servant: Insights and Poems [2 of 2]1971 - 1975 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Co-Authorship of Book with Angela Davis and Ericka Huggins 1972 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Ericka Huggins - Poems Mss; Introduction - Angela Davis [1 of 2]1969 - 1973 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Ericka Huggins - Poems Mss; Introduction - Angela Davis [2 of 2]1969 - 1973 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Ericka Huggins, Poetry, Fire and Rain1969 - 1972 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - George Jackson
      - George Jackson's Letters1968 - 1970 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Article From George Jackson 1970 (Box 44, Folder 12)
        New York Times
      - Newton - Prior Conviction 1977 (Box 44, Folder 13)
        Last will and testament
      - George Jackson - Letters1968 - 1971 (Box 44, Folder 14)
        information regarding the estate of George Jackson
      - George Jackson - Agreements1971 - 1972 (Box 44, Folder 15)
        Stronghold items
      - George Jackson's Books1971 - 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1)
        preface to "Solidad Brothers" plus contracts and agreements
      - George Jackson Commemorative Poster1970 - 1972 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Folder 4: George Jackson1971 (Box 45, Folder 3)
        last will and testament plus case #12848 ( State of Ca vs Hugo A Pinell, et al)
      - Blood in My Eye1971 - 1972 (Box 45, Folder 4)
        contracts and agreements
      - George Jackson - 2nd Book of Letters1971 - 1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - George Jackson Estate - Agreements1971 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Letter accompanying review of Blood in My Eye1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - For Servant: From Eric Mann - Series Articles on George Jackson [1 of 2]1971 (Box 45, Folder 8)
        from "The Phoenix" (Boston, Sept. 14, 1971)
      - For Servant: From Eric Mann - Series Articles on George Jackson [2 of 2]1971 (Box 45, Folder 9)
        from "The Phoenix" (Boston, Sept. 21 and 28, 1971)
      - Notes on the Assassination of George Jackson (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - [Writings of George Jackson from "Blood in My Eye" - typed manuscripts] [1 of 2]1971 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - [Writings of George Jackson from "Blood in My Eye" - typed manuscripts] [2 of 2]1971 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Darthard Perry (Othello)
      - Othello - A.K.A. D. Perry1980 (Box 45, Folder 13)
        "The Confessions of Othello" plus other items
      - Othello Transcript by Roger Rapoport #2 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Declaration of Darthard Perry, a.k.a Othello1975 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Bobby Seale
      - Info. From Bobby and Ericka 1970 - 1971 (Box 45, Folder 16)
        letters and memos regarding the split of the party
      - Bobby Seale For Mayor of Oakland [1 of 2]1972 - 1973 (Box 45, Folder 17)
        articles plus an issue of "Jet" (vol. XLIV, no. 3, April 12, 1973)
      - Bobby Seale For Mayor of Oakland [2 of 2]1972 - 1973 (Box 45, Folder 18)
        articles
      - Bobby Seale Campaign Info. [1 of 9]1972 - 1973 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Bobby Seale Campaign Info. [2 of 9]1972 - 1973 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Bobby Seale Campaign Info. [3 of 9]1972 - 1973 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Bobby Seale Campaign Info. [4 of 9]1972 - 1973 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Bobby Seale Campaign Info. [5 of 9]1972 - 1973 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Bobby Seale Campaign Info. [6 of 9]1972 - 1973 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Bobby Seale Campaign Info. [7 of 9]1972 - 1973 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Bobby Seale Campaign Info. [8 of 9]1972 - 1973 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Bobby Seale Campaign Info. [9 of 9]1972 - 1973 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Seize the Time - Seale - Dist. Figures1972 (Box 46, Folder 9)
        sales numbers of the book
      - "Conversations with Bobby Seale"1971 (Box 46, Folder 10)
        Bobby Seale speaks with Arthur Goldberg of Ramparts magazine plus contracts and agreements
      - Survey: Redding/Seale & Brown Campaign (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - [Bobby Seale - A Lonely Rage]1979 - 1980 (Box 46, Folder 12)
        advertising piece about the book
      - Bobby Seale on Quake - Oakland Tribune Dec. 8, 1989 1989 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Seale [Seize the Time Tax Materials]1971 - 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Johnny Spain
      - Spain1971 (Box 47, Folder 2)
        "On the Indeterminate Sentencing";"On Being Revolutionary"
      - Johnny Spain1976 - 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
        case #16126 plus other items
      - Johnny Spain - Corresp. With Publ. & E. Brown1972 - 1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Writings by Johnny Spain1970 - 1971 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - [A prisoner dreams, by Johnny Spain]1974 - 1975 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - [Article on Johnny Spain] (Box 47, Folder 7)
        from "Frisko"
      - Unshackled - Johnnie Spain1989 (Box 47, Folder 8)
        newspaper articles
    - Louis Tackwood
      - Louis Tackwood's Testimony1970 - 1976 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - The Glass House Tapes - Part II (Box 47, Folder 10)
        second draft - Part II The Witness
      - The Glass House Tapes by Louis Tackwood and Don Freed [1 of 2] (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - The Glass House Tapes by Louis Tackwood and Don Freed [2 of 2] (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Professional Security Consultants Re: Louis Tackwood 10/711971 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Tackwood Deposition1976 (Box 47, Folder 14)
        case #63447
      - [Krasener, et al. vs. Bingham, et al. / Deposition of Louis Tackwood]1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - [Louis Tackwood, Misc. Legal Information] (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 8: Reference materials, 8
    - Information Re: Africa1977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      Federal Nigeria (vol. 3, no. 1, Apr-Jun 1977; vol. 4, no. 1, Jul-Sept 1977);Nigeria Review (no. 3, no. 9 1977);letters and flyers
    - Washington Notes on Africa "Reagan and Africa, Winter 1980/19811980 - 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - [Articles on South Africa ]1970 - 1971 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - American Committee on Africa1970 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - African Research Group1967 - 1970 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      Radical Study Guide, Go to School Learn to Rule the Yale Method;various flyers, articles and letters ;(including a letter to Caesar Chavez from the BPP re: Cal-Pac Boycott of Gallo)
    - Congress of African People1970 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      information from the Annual Conference, Sept. 3-7, 1970
    - (Summary) Life and Development Among the Earliest Humans in Africa 1966 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      summary of article in Tarikh (vol. 1, no. 3, pp. 12-19)
    - (Summary) Concepts of God in Africa1970 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      summary of Chapter 8 from John Mbitit's Concepts of God in Africa
    - When the Panthers Came to Yale (1970)1970 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      article from NY Times Magazine June 21, 1970
    - Write-ups On Our Books1970; 1973 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      various newspaper articles
    - [Articles about the Black Panthers in Ramparts]1968 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      Ramparts (Jul 13, 1968 and Oct 26, 1968);plus Huey's Birthday card with photos of children
    - [Essay and booklet on CIA's organizational history]1978 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - New York Times Article 3/17/78 CIA vs. BPP1978 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Center for National Security Studies COINTELPRO in Court, by J. Peterzell1978 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      article's from vol. 4, no. 3, 1978
    - [COINTELPRO]1974 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      also Information Digest (Aug. 23, 1974)
    - [COINTELPRO] [1 of 3] (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - [COINTELPRO] [2 of 3] (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - [COINTELPRO] [3 of 3] (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - [FBI ]1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - [Articles about FBI]1978; 1981 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      articles from feed/back (Spring 1978), Essence (Oct. 1978), Newsweek (Nov. 30, 1981)
    - Freedom of Information Act1976 - 1977 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Martin L. King, Jr. Case Study by FBI (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Press View The FBI Raid [Re: FBI RAID of July 8, 1977 on The Church of Scientology]1974; 1977 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      also copy of Ku Klux Klan pamphlet and death certificate of Kathleen Smith
    - FBI Plot Against Black Leaders - Essence Magazine (Oct.)1978 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Investigating the FBI Committee for Public Justice (1973)1973 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      copy of Chapter 2: The History of the FBI: Democracy's Development of a Secret Police
    - Subcommittee to Investigate the Administration of the Internal Security Act and other Internal Security Laws1971 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      tesimony of Thomas Edward Mosher
    - Correspondence from Security & Intelligence Fund1980 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Deception in Psychological Research - Security and Intelligence 1980 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Gun Barrel Politics The BPP -1966-1971 Comm. On Internal Security [1 of 2] (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Gun Barrel Politics The BPP -1966-1971 Comm. On Internal Security [2 of 2] (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - The American Inquisition 1977 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      published by the US Ministerial Conference of Scientology Ministers
    - Mechanics of Repression - J. Edgar Hoover Crime & Social Justice1977 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      Crime and Social Justice (Spring-Summer 1977)
    - (Summary) The Police on Skid-Row: A Study of Peace-Keeping1967 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      summary from article by Egon Bittner in American Sociological Review (Oct. 1967)
    - The Winter Soldier Investigation (An Inquiry Into U.S. War Crimes in Vietnam) (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Study of Religious Discrimination Submission to the US Comm. On Civil RIghts (Box 49, Folder 19)
      presented by the Council of Scientology Ministers
    - The Red Squad Detroit, Michigan [1 of 4] (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - The Red Squad Detroit, Michigan [2 of 4] (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - The Red Squad Detroit, Michigan [3 of 4] (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - The Red Squad Detroit, Michigan [4 of 4] (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - [Relative Responsibility in California: A Report to the State Legislature]1975 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      "Relative Responsibility in California: A Report to the State Legislature," Prepared by Peter D. Coppleman and Fred J. Hiestand, Attorneys at Law, 1970 Broadway, Suite 1215, Oakland, California 94612, for the Assembly Rules Committee, California State Legislature, September 12, 1975
    - Department of Employment - Information [1 of 2]1967 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      "Preliminary Tabulations from the 701 Sample Census of Oakland, Characteristics of the Population of Oakland, California 1966, Prepared for the Department of Employment State of California" by The Survey Research Center University of California, Berkeley, December 2, 1966, William L. Nicholls II, Study Director
    - Department of Employment - Information [2 of 2]1967 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      "California Employment and Payrolls: A Report of Workers and Wages Covered by the California Unemployment Insurance Code," Report 127, no. 28d, October - December, 1965, Department of Employment, State of California, Edmund G. Brown, Governor
    - Lie Detector Test Methodology (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - [Socialist Workers Party, et al vs. Attorney General of the United States, et al] (Box 50, Folder 9)
      United States District Court Southern District of New York;Socialist Workers Party, et al., Plaintiffs, v. Attorney General of the United States, et al.;73 Civ. 3160 (TPG)
    - National Conference of Black Lawyers [1 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 10)
      Nathaniel Omar. "Lennox Hinds: Serving the People's Interest," Bilalian News (March 11, 1977),7;NCBL Notes, 2:4 (Fall 1976), 3:1 (Spring 1977), 2:3 (Summer 1976).;National Conference of Black Lawyers Report of the National Director, 1976 by Lennox S. Hinds, National Director
    - National Conference of Black Lawyers [2 of 2] (Box 50, Folder 11)
      "International Commission of Enquiry on Mercenaries, Luanda, Angola: The Trial of the Mercenaries, June 7 - 19, 1976," A Special Report Prepared by Lennox S. Hinds, National Director; Hope R. Stevens, Co-Chairperson Board of Directors, National Conference of Black Lawyers
    - National Lawyers Guild Convention Feb. 1979 S.F.1979 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      "National Lawyers Guild Convention," February 1979, A People's Guide to San Francisco - Bay Area
    - Indiana Law Review Vol. 10 No.2 19771977 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - The Indeterminate Sentence Law and Its Debilitating Effects (Box 51, Folder 3)
      Bobby Dorado. "The Indeterminate Sentence Law and Its Duplicating Effects," Introduction
    - Remarks at the People's World Banquet Oct.11, 19701970 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      "Remarks at the People's World Banquet Oct.11, 1970," Franklin Alexander, Chairman, Che-Lumumba Club, CPUSS
    - L.A. Black Leadership Conference; Ted Watkins, Watts Labor Action Committee June 25th to 27th, 1971 1971 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - On the Military Aspect of the American Revolution (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Intercommunal Committee to Combat Fascism1972 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      "Intercommunal Committee to Combat Fascism," Palo Alto, California, 14 January 1972
    - Information to the Community on Jury Selection and Participation1971 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      Donald Freed. "The Jurors' Handbook," table of contents and editor's notes.
    - News of the Day [1 of 2]1972 - 1973 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - News of the Day [2 of 2]1972 - 1973 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Media [1 of 2] (Box 51, Folder 11)
      Television Digest February, 1972: Final Cable Television Decision Adopted by Federal Communications Commission February 2, 1972, Issued February 3, 1972 Establishing Rules and Standards for Cable Television Operations
    - Media [2 of 2] (Box 51, Folder 12)
      Herbert S. Dordick and Jack Lyle. R-881-MF, November 1971, "Access by Local Political Candidates to Cable Television: A Report of an Experiment" A Report prepared under a Grant from the John and Mary R. Markle Foundation (Santa Monica, CA: Rand Corporation, 1971).; H. Allan Fredericksen. Community Access Video. (n.p.: 1972).
    - Notes on Magazine Article1970 - 1972 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - [Foreign language writings about the Panthers] [1 of 5] (Box 51, Folder 14)